Sanctuary Movement Trial papers, 1979-1992
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
Sanctuary Movement Trial papers, 1981-1992
MS 362
A. Bates Butler (attorney for Phillip Conger),; James Brosnahan (attorney for Maria Socorro de Aguilar),; Michael Altman (attorney for Darlene Nicgorski),; Peg Hutchison,; Arizona American Friends Service Committee (Jim Corbett),; Southside Presbyterian Church (John Fife)
The Sanctuary Movement was a religious and political campaign that began in the early 1980s to provide safety for Central American refugees fleeing civil conflicts within their home countries. This collection contains materials related to the Sanctuary Movement and, more specifically, the highly publicized Sanctuary Trial that took place in Arizona. Within the collection are attorney files, certified trial transcripts, publicity materials, and trial notebooks. Also represented in the collection are donated materials from the American Friends Service Committee and the Southside Presbyterian Church, who were important players in the Sanctuary Movement. Materials from these organizations include correspondence, newspaper clippings, publications and trial materials.
73.5 linear feet
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections University of Arizona PO Box 210055 Tucson, AZ 85721-0055 Phone: 520-621-6423 Fax: 520-621-9733 URL: http://www.library.arizona.edu/speccoll
Restrictions
Several series in this collection contain restrictions. Series IV “A” Files box 5-folders 38-44 and box 6; Series VII Trial Transcripts, Subseries 3 Operation Sojourner Transcripts box 15-folder 29-36, box 16 and box 17-folders 1-8; and Series VII Trial Transcripts, Subseries 4 Certified Trial Transcripts box 20-folder 15 and box 21-folders 9 and 14 which are sealed by court order.
Historical Note
The Sanctuary Movement can trace its beginnings to the early 1980s when concerned citizens such as Jim Corbett, John Fife, Phillip Conger and others began helping refugees from Central America (El Salvador, Guatemala, Honduras, and Nicaragua) seek political asylum. These men and others began helping refugees avoid capture by the United States Government. Jim Corbett, a Quaker, insisted that what they were doing was not “civil disobedience.” He argued instead that it was “civil initiative” -- they were upholding laws regarding treatment of war refugees that the U.S. government refused to enforce.
The movement started along the border with Mexico and Arizona, but was also represented in Chicago, Philadelphia, California and Texas. On March 24, 1982, Southside Presbyterian under the direction of Reverend John Fife became the first church in the country to declare itself a sanctuary for Central Americans fleeing persecution. The movement quickly gained attention and acceptance. At its height, more than 200 religious orders (Christian and non-Christian) and congregations nationwide, several universities and municipalities, and more than 600 religious organizations, including the National Federation of Priests’ Councils (representing more than 33,000 Catholic priests) declared themselves in favor of sanctuary.
Rejecting the claim that sanctuary was in fact upholding the law, the U.S. government moved against its leaders. In January 1985, 11 members of the Sanctuary Movement, including two Catholic priests and several religious lay workers, were indicted on alien-smuggling charges. After a six-month trial in Tucson, eight were convicted of various felonies. All received probation. The verdict was filed in March 1988 and taken to the Ninth U.S. Circuit Court of Appeals in San Francisco. The court upheld the convictions and in 1991 the U.S Supreme Court left intact the ruling by the U.S Circuit Court of Appeals.
Organization
This collection is organized into ten series:
Series 1: Indexes no date
Series 2: Background/Pretrial Material 1981-1987
Series 3: Individuals no date
Series 4: "A" Files ca. 1985
Series 5: Count Files no date
Series 6: Trial Notebooks ca. 1985
Series 7: Trial Transcripts no date
Subseries 1: Pre-trial Transcripts no date
Subseries 2: Depositions no date
Subseries 3: Operation Sojourner no date
Subseries 4: Certified Trial Transcripts no date
Subseries 5: Trial Summaries no date
Subseries 6: Post-verdict Sentencing no date
Series 8: American Friends Society Committee (AFSC) 1982-1989
Series 9: Southside Presbyterian Church no date
Series 10: Newspaper Clippings 1981-1988
Series 11: Appeal Materials 1981-1989
Subseries 1: Assorted Background and Appeal Materials 1981-1988
Subseries 2: Legal Briefs 1981-1988
Subseries 3: Motions and Government Responses 1981-1988
Subseries 4: Peggy Hutchinson Files 1981-1988
Series 12: Background/ Pretrial Material 1981-1991
Subseries 1: Assorted Background/Pretrial Materials 1981-1991
Subseries 2: Background--Guatemala 1981-1991
Subseries 3: Background--Related Cases (Texas) 1981-1991
Series 13: Individuals 1981-1991
Series 14: Post-Trial Miscellaneous Materials 1982-1992
Series 15: Newspaper Clippings 1979-1992
Scope and Content Note
The inclusive dates for this collection are 1982-1992. The materials in the collection relate to the Sanctuary Movement, but more specifically the Sanctuary Trial that took place in Arizona. This collection is a compilation of materials received from several lawyers and local organizations that were involved in the Sanctuary Movement. As a result, there was much duplication. To assist the researcher as much as possible, duplicates were discarded and only one copy was kept. Materials received from the attorneys have been organized into the first seven series. Series eight and nine consist of materials from various organizations, and series ten is a collection of newspaper clippings maintained by the attorneys also. The 2012 addendum consists of materials pertaining to the appeal case, the defendants Peggy Hutchinson and Wendy LeWin. Other items can be found like trial materials which include background/pretrial materials as well as additional materials on individuals that relate to Series two and three. Also included in the Amendum are miscellaneous documents collected after the trial such as church pamphlets, support letters, and newspaper clippings which relate to Series 10 as well.
Series one “Indexes,” contains indexes kept by the lawyers regarding the defendants, general information, and the Sanctuary Movement itself.
Series two “Background/Pre-trial material,” consists of background and pre-trial material. Included in this series are government interviews, information about government witnesses, phone logs/bills, reports, and materials relating to the Sanctuary Defense Fund.
Series three “Individuals,” contains materials collected by the attorney’s regarding individuals related to this case. This section contains items regarding the defendants, government witnesses, government informants, un-indicted/co-conspirators, and others involved in the case.
Series four “’A’ Files” contains files regarding illegal or legal aliens that have a direct bearing on the case. These files contain personal information regarding these individuals. This series is restricted.
Series five “Counts,” contains the charges or “counts” against the 11 who were indicted.
Series six “Trial Notebooks,” contains the trial notebooks kept by the attorney’s. Included in these notebooks are information about defendants (Phillip Conger and Sister Darlene Nicgorski), government informant Jesus Cruz, jury instructions, subpoenas, and general information regarding the Sanctuary Movement.
Series seven “Trial Transcripts,” contains the certified trial transcripts and is divided into six sub-series. Sub-series one consists of pre-trial transcripts (motions), sub-series two consists of depositions, sub-series three consists of the taped transcripts of “Operation Sojourner.” This sub-series also contains notes taken by the attorneys regarding these transcripts. This sub-series is restricted. Sub-series four contains the certified trial transcripts that lasted from October 1985-May 1986. Box 20, folder 15 and Box 21, folder 9 and 14 are restricted. Sub-series five contains trial summaries and sub-series six contains the post-verdict sentencing transcripts.
Series eight “American Friends Service Committee,” contains materials given by American Friends Service Committee (AFSC). These materials highlight Jim Corbett’s involvement in the Sanctuary Movement and contain articles by or about Corbett, legal/trial material regarding Corbett, news clippings, and videos.
Series nine “Southside Presbyterian Church,” contains materials given by the Southside Presbyterian Church (SPC). These materials were collected over a period of time and reflect articles, correspondence, new clippings, publications, and reports regarding the Sanctuary Movement. Many of these items highlight SPC’s involvement in the movement.
Series ten “Newspaper Clippings,” contains newspaper clippings collected between 1981 and 1988 regarding the Sanctuary movement, trial, and world events as they relate to this case.
Series eleven “Appeals” This series contains important materials pertaining to the appeal of the trial, including legal briefs, correspondence, notes, and various files that were compiled by the attorneys. The various motions filed during the appeal are represented as well as government responses to those motions. Since Peggy Hutchinson was one of the donors, her files are highly represented; however, some materials from the other appellants can be found in this series as well. Materials and duplicates pertaining to the original sanctuary trial case are present in this series, especially since these materials were used as research and to strengthen the appeal case. These materials can be found mostly in Subseries one and Subseries three.
Series twelve “Background/Pretrial Material” These materials are additions and extensions of Series Two. The first subseries contains assorted materials that include trial documents, such as attorney notes and trial exhibits, and topics associated with the Sanctuary movement, such as different organizations that participated in the movement. Subseries Two is focused on materials about Guatemala. The dominant materials in this subseries are bulletins and newsletters from various organizations and associations within Guatemala or in support of Guatemala in the movement. Subseries Three includes materials about the related Sanctuary movement trial that took place in Texas. Most of the materials in this series are depositions; however, there are also trial materials including briefs and motions.
Series Thirteen “Individuals” The materials in this collection specifically pertain to the defendant Peggy Hutchinson and her attorney, Michael Piccarreta, and the defendant Wendy LeWin and her attorney Ellen Yaroshefsky. This is an addition to Series Three. The series contains pleading files, correspondence, and other materials pertinent to the case. Other materials represented in this series are files related to the Sanctuary movement, such as the Arizona Sanctuary Defense Fund, and files dealing with outside projects important to the defendants.
Series fourteen “Post-Trial Miscellaneous Material” The materials in this collection were collected after the trial and include examples of support such as Junior High student’s support letters, church pamphlets and various organizations dealings with the movement and trial.
Series fifteen “Newspaper Clippings, 1979-1992” Clippings are collected from various regions.
Items in this collection can be found both in English and in Spanish.
Access Terms
Sanctuary Movement -- Arizona -- Tucson
Church and social problems -- Arizona -- Tucson
Christianity and politics
Political refugees -- Central America
Church work with refugees -- United States
Corbett, Jim, 1933-
Fife, John M. (John Macmillan), 1940-
Church and state -- United States
Asylum, Right of -- United States
Container List
- Series 1: Indexes, no date
  - Indexes--Defendants (part one), no date (Box 1, type="folder">1)
  - Indexes--Defendants (part two), no date (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Indexes--General (p. 1-65), no date (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Indexes--General (p. 66-end), no date (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Indexes--Sanctuary., no date (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Series 2: Background/Pretrial Material, 1981-1987
  - Background--Amnesty International, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Background--Broadway Christian Church, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Background--Broadway Christian Church, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Background--Broadway Christian Church--Correspondence, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Background--CRIE (Centro Regional de Informaciones Ecumenicas), 1983-1985 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Background--Center for Constitutional Rights, 1982-1985 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Background--Central American Refugee Defense Fund, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Background--Canadian Asylum, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Background--CDHS (Comision de Derechos Humanos en El Salvador), no date (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Background--Church World Service, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Background--Conger, Phillip, no date (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Background--Congress--Hearings, November 7, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Background-- Freedom Sadder, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Background--Guatemala, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Background--Government Interview--Chase, Charles A., Jr., June 8,1985 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Background--Government Interview--Coffin, Roberts, June 8, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Background--Government Interview--Cruz, Jesus, June 8, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Background--Government Interview--Dunlap, Arthur K., June 7,1985 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Background--Government Interview--Graham, Salomon, June 8,1985 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Background--Government Interview--Rayburn, James, June 8,1985 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Background--Government Interview--Reed, Mark Kevin, June 7,1985 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Background--Government Witnesses, no date (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Background--Immigration and Nationality Act, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Background--Immigration Newsletter, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Background--INS (Immigration & NaturalizationService)--Asylum Adjudications, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Background--INS reports, no date (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Background--INS reports, no date (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Background--Indexes, no date (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Background--Index of Exhibits, no date (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Background--Jury Instructions, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Background--National Defense Fund--Media Packet, no date (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Background--Newsletter, Clergy and Laity for Central America, 1981-1984 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Background--Nicgorski, Sister Darlene--Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Background--Nicgorski, Sister Darlene--Handouts, no date (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Background--Nicgorski, Sister Darlene--Notebook, no date (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Background--Notes, no date (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Background--Opening Statement, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Background--Overt Acts & Indictment, no date (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Background--Pamphlets--Border Patrol, no date (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Background--Phone bills, 1982-1985 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Background--Phone bills, 1982-1985 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Background--Phone bills, 1982-1985 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Background--Phone bills, 1982-1985 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Background--Photographs, no date (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Background--Refugee Legislation (part one), no date (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Background--Refugee Legislation (part two), no date (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Background--Related Cases (California), no date (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Background--Related Cases (Texas), no date (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Background--Reports, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Background--Reports, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Background--Reports, no date (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Background--Reports--Amnesty International, no date (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Background--Reports-- As Bad As Ever..., 1984 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Background--Reports-- Criteria for the Determination of Refugee Status, no date (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Background--Reports--El Salvador, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Background--Reports--El Salvador, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Background--Reports-- El Salvador: One Year of Oppression, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Background--Reports-- Report of Tribunal, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Background--Reports-- Salvadoran Rightists, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Background--Sanctuary, no date (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Background--Sanctuary Book Committee, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Background--Sanctuary--National Mailing, no date (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Background--Sanctuary Defense Fund, no date (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Background--Sanctuary Defense Fund--Articles of Incorporation, no date (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Background--Sanctuary Defense Fund--By-Laws, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Background--Sanctuary Defense Fund--Correspondence, 1985-1987 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Background--Sanctuary Defense Fund--Media Packets, no date (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Background--Sanctuary Defense Fund--News clippings, no date (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Background--Sanctuary Defense Fund--Tax Exempt Status, no date (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Background--Sanctuary Defense Fund--Trust Agreement, no date (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Background--Sanctuary Movement--Declaration of Sanctuary, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Background--Sanctuary Movement--Meetings, no date (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Background--Sanctuary Movement--Memos, no date (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Background--Sanctuary Movement--Policy/Proposals, no date (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Background--Sanctuary Movement--Practical Information, no date (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Background--Sanctuary Movement--Press Releases, no date (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Background--Sanctuary Movement--Refugees Commitment, no date (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Background--Sanctuary Movement--Refugee Questionnaire, no date (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Background--Sanctuary Movement--Testimonies, no date (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Background--Songs/Poems, no date (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Series 3: Individuals, no date
  - Borreno, Manuel, no date (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Campo, Douglas, no date (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Campo, Francesca, no date (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Cassoli, Jennifer (or Michelle), no date (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Clark, Father Anthony, no date (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Conger, Ellen, no date (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Cook, Reverend Donovan, no date (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Delgado, Salvador, no date (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Defendant--Aguilar, Maria del Socorro, no date (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Defendant--Fife, Reverend John, no date (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Defendant--Nicgorski, Sister Darlene, no date (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Defendant--Nicgorski, Sister Darlene, no date (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Defendant--Nicgorski, Sister Darlene, no date (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Defendant--Nicgorski, Sister Darlene, no date (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Defendant--Nicgorski, Sister Darlene, no date (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Defendant--Nicgorski, Sister Darlene, no date (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Defendant--Nicgorski, Sister Darlene, no date (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Defendant--Nicgorski, Sister Darlene, no date (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Emery, Cecelia, no date (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Government Witness--Antonio, Ana, no date (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Government Witness--Antonio, Ana, no date (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Government Witness--Benavides, Ana Trinidad, no date (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Government Witness--Benavides, Julio Cesar, no date (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Government Witness-- Barvaza de Gomez, Leticia, no date (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Government Witness--Cruz, Jesus, no date (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Government Witness--Doyle, Reverend, no date (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Government Witness--Elford, Padre Ricardo, no date (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Government Witness--Graham, Salomon, no date (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Government Witness--Guevarra-Benavides, Julio Cesar, no date (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Government Witness--Jose Antonio, no date (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Government Witness--Kelly, Kay, no date (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Government Witness--Lockwood, George, no date (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Government Witness--Lopez, Gabriela, no date (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Government Witness--Lopez, Jose Morales, no date (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Government Witness--Mejia-Barrera, Miguel Angel, no date (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Government Witness--Morgan, Lee, no date (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Government Witness--Munez-Villatoro, Candida Natalia, no date (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Informants--PHO-I-98 (part one), no date (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Informants--PHO-I-98 (part two), no date (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Informants--PHO-I-92, no date (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Letson, Shadi, no date (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Lundy, Mary Ann, no date (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Lopez, Elba, no date (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Nonn, Tim, no date (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Pheil, Clifford, no date (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Pheil, Sharron, no date (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Priester, Sister Ana, no date (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Rayburn, James, no date (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Rayburn, James, no date (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Ristad, Adam, no date (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Rodriguez, Jorge, no date (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Tung, Ching Kuan, no date (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Tung, Shirley, no date (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Vasquiz, Sister Maria Luisa, no date (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Waddel, Sister Mary, no date (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Wann, John William, no date (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Win, Wendy Le, no date (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Various "A,", no date (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Various "B,", no date (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Various "C,", no date (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Various "D,", no date (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Various "E,", no date (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Various "F,", no date (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Various "G,", no date (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Various "H-I,", no date (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Various "J-L,", no date (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Various "M,", no date (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Various "N-Q,", no date (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Various "R,", no date (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Various "S,", no date (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Various "T-Z,", no date (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Various, no date (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Series 4: "A" Files, ca. 1985
  This series is restricted.
  - Acebedo-Gaytan, Ulesas, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Alfaro-Portillo, Gabriel, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Alvarez-Maroquin, Genaro, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Alvarez-Maroquin, Louis Fernando, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Arevalo-Samoyoa, Mario, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Canenquez, Jose R., 1985 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Demorales, Clara, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Barrazza de Gomez, Leticia, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Benavides Martel, Julio Cesar, no date (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Benavides Martel, Ana, no date (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Benavidez-Rodriguez, Bertha, no date (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Benitez, Julio Cesar, no date (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Calderon Recinos, Luis Alfonso, no date (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Chamorro de Hernandez, Miriam, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Cruz-Antonio, Fredrico, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Cruz-Benavides, Regina de la, no date (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Cruz-Jimenez, Juan, no date (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Dheming, Roberto Manuel, no date (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Dheming-Padilla, Manuel, no date (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Flores-Mejia, Jesus Elmer, no date (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Francisco-Mendez, Cecelia, no date (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Garcia, Roberto, no date (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Gomez-Montana, Alejandro, no date (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Guevara-Benavidez, Julio Cesar, no date (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Hernandez-Argueta, Rosa Adelia, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Huezo Velasquez de Calderon, Sandra, no date (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Jose y Gabriela, no date (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Lazo-Hernandez, Jose Carlos, no date (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Lemos de Villeda, Maria Luz, no date (Box 6, Folder 22)